https://www.pacificcoast.com/customer-service/privacy-policy.html/privacy-policy.html

SEARCH
Your Cart : (0)
Pacific Coast Feather Company Privacy Policy
At Pacific Coast Feather Company, we are committed to ensuring the privacy of our customers. This privacy policy explains our privacy practices for our customers who visit our web site at www.pacificcoast.com. By using our web site, you consent to the terms of this privacy policy. You may read about the details of our privacy policy below.
What is Personal Information?
Personal information is information that specifically identifies an individual such as a customer's name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card or other account number, and information about that individual's activities when directly linked to that person such as information about his or her purchases. Personal information also includes demographic information such as date of birth, gender, geographic area and preferences when such information is linked to other personal information that identifies you.
Personal information does not include "aggregate" information. Aggregate information is data we collect about a group or category of products, services or customers, from which individual customer identities have been removed. In other words, information about how you use a service may be collected and combined with information about how others use the same service, but no personal information will be included in the resulting data. Likewise, information about the products you purchase may be collected and combined with information about the products purchased by others. Aggregate data helps us understand trends and customer needs so that we can better consider new products and services, and tailor existing products and services to customer desires.
Personal Information We Collect
You provide personal information in a number of ways when you visit our web site. For example, you provide us with personal information when you: (1) purchase products; (2) register and set up an Account; (3) sign up for our e-mail newsletter; (4) submit a warranty registration; or (5) contact us by e-mail for any reason. When you visit our web site, some information is also automatically collected, such as your computer's Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer's operating system, the browser type, the address of a referring web site, and the time and date of your visit and purchases. This information may be collected through the use of "cookies" or other devices (See Online Specifics below). We treat this information as personal information if we combine it with or link it to any of the identifying information mentioned above. Otherwise, it is used in the aggregate only.
How We Use Personal Information.
In general, we use personal information to process your requests or transactions and provide you with high-quality service or to inform you about other products or services we think will be of interest. For example, we may use your account information to deliver products you have purchased or if you purchase a pillow on our web site, we may send you materials on how to wash and care for that pillow. When we use personal information in our marketing efforts, we provide you with choices (See Choice below) and do not disclose the information to third parties except as described in this privacy policy. Personal information provided online may be linked together or merged with other personal information so that we may better understand your needs and inform you about our products or services and those of our partners. In addition, if we receive information from third parties with whom we have business relationships, we may combine this information with the other personal information we maintain about you. In either case, this privacy policy governs this information.
Security
We have put into place reasonable security measures in an effort to protect personal information while it is under our control. All personal information relating to our customers is stored in a secure environment separate from our web site. Orders placed on our web site are protected by an encryption technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), to ensure privacy and security when submitting an order. Your account information is accessible online only through the use of a password. To protect the confidentiality of personal information, you must keep your password confidential and not disclose it to any other person. You are responsible for all uses of our web site by any person using your password. Please advise us immediately if you believe your password has been misused.
Choice
We give you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and to view, correct or delete your personal information.
1. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, you can; (a) click on 'My Account' on any page of our web site and alter your preferences accordingly; or (b) if you do not have an Account, click on the 'Customer Service' and 'Services' links on our web site and follow the directions that appear on the screen
2. If you do not want to receive mail from us, you can: (a) e-mail us at comfort@pacificcoast.com or (b) write to us at
Pacific Coast Feather Company
1964 4th Ave S.
Seattle, WA 98134
3. If you want to view, correct or delete your personal information, you can access your account information online by clicking on the 'My Account' link on any page of our web site.
4. For other requests or to contact us directly, see Questions or Concerns below.
Sharing of Personal Information
We do not sell, rent or share personal information with third parties without your prior consent except in the limited circumstances described in this privacy policy. We may share personal information with third-party vendors who assist us in performing internal functions necessary to operate our business. These functions may include sending promotional e-mails on our behalf, serving advertisements on our behalf, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments; and fulfilling and delivering orders. In all cases we limit the information shared with our third-party vendors to that which is necessary to carry out those functions. Moreover, we require them to comply with our privacy practices, keep the information confidential and not to use it for other purposes except as required by law. We are not responsible for any additional information you provide directly to these parties, and we encourage you to become familiar with their practices before disclosing information directly to them.
In addition, we may disclose personal information in the good faith belief that we are lawfully authorized to do so, or that doing so is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process or authorities, respond to any claims, or to protect the rights, property or personal safety of Pacific Coast Feather Co., our customers, our employees or the public. Information about our customers, including personal information, may be disclosed or transferred as part of, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets or acquisition.
Online Specifics
1. Cookies
We shall only store so called “cookies” on your computer when you have provided us with your consent by clicking on the appropriate button(s) during your visit of our website. Cookies are small text files that the website stores locally on your computer. Cookies allow us to recognize your computer the next time you visit us. By doing so, PCF is able to improve user-friendliness of the website and to adjust the website to your needs. Most Internet browsers are set to accept these cookies automatically.
The type of personal information we collect as a result of a cookie is specific to your device and may include the Internet Protocol (IP) address, the date and time you access our website and what parts of the website are visited. We collect the foregoing personal information to monitor the usage and usefulness of our website, for statistical purposes and to send you information about our company and our (new) products and services, which suit your interest.
You may set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie or to refuse receiving it. You can also withdraw your consent at all times by re-entering our website and select the right options. By changing settings, you can also determine that your browser will not accept cookies from this website. Be aware that in such events you may no longer be able to use all the possibilities and features of our website.
Use of our Web Site by Children
We encourage parents to take an active interest in their children's use of the Internet. We do not intend to collect information from children who are under 18 years of age. If you are under 18, you should not provide information on our web site and should ask your parent to do so for you.
Links to Other Web Sites
Our web site contains links to other web sites. Any personal information you provide on the linked pages is provided directly to that third party and is subject to that third party's privacy policy. Except as described above, we are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of web sites to which we link. Links from our web site to third parties or to other sites are provided for your convenience. We encourage you to learn about their privacy and security practices and policies before providing them with personal information.
Your Comments or Concerns
We welcome your feedback. If you have any comments or concerns about this privacy policy or would like to contact us for any reason, you may reach a customer service representative via e-mail at comfort@pacificcoast.com, phone at 1-888-297-1778, or message us through the Contact Us page.
Policy Changes
We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time. We may use personal information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in this privacy policy. If our privacy practices change we will post the policy changes to our web site and notify you by indicating the date the privacy policy was last updated. We will also provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. We encourage you to check back at our web site periodically if you are concerned about how your information is used.
Secondary Navigation
About Our Company
Affiliate Program
Privacy Policy
Terms of Use
Contact Us
Care Instructions
Frequent Questions
